[
	{
		"question": "1 - 1 + 1 * 1 + 1",
		"choice1": "1",
		"choice2": "2",
		"choice3": "3",
		"choice4": "4",
		"answer": "c2"
	},
	{
		"question": "2 * 2 / 2 + 2",
		"choice1": "1",
		"choice2": "2",
		"choice3": "3",
		"choice4": "4",
		"answer": "c4"
	},
	{
		"question": "3 + 3 ** 3",
		"choice1": "6",
		"choice2": "9",
		"choice3": "30",
		"choice4": "216",
		"answer": "c3"
	},
	{
		"question": "4 * 4 + 4 * 4",
		"choice1": "4",
		"choice2": "16",
		"choice3": "32",
		"choice4": "256",
		"answer": "c3"
	},
	{
		"question": "5 / 5 / 5 / 5",
		"choice1": "1",
		"choice2": "2",
		"choice3": "0.02",
		"choice4": "0.04",
		"answer": "c4"
	},
	{
		"question": "6 - 6 - 6 - 6",
		"choice1": "-12",
		"choice2": "-18",
		"choice3": "-24",
		"choice4": "-32",
		"answer": "c1"
	},
	{
		"question": "7**7/7**7",
		"choice1": "0",
		"choice2": "1",
		"choice3": "Infinity",
		"choice4": "-Infinity",
		"answer": "c3"
	},
	{
		"question": "- 8 + 8 + 8 + 8",
		"choice1": "0",
		"choice2": "8",
		"choice3": "16",
		"choice4": "24",
		"answer": "c3"
	},
	{
		"question": "9 - 9 / 9 - 9",
		"choice1": "-1",
		"choice2": "1",
		"choice3": "0",
		"choice4": "0.11",
		"answer": "c1"
	},
	{
		"question": "0 ** 0 ** 0",
		"choice1": "0",
		"choice2": "1",
		"choice3": "Infinity",
		"choice4": "-Infinity",
		"answer": "c1"
	},
	{
		"question": "4 ** 3 * 2 + 1",
		"choice1": "128",
		"choice2": "129",
		"choice3": "163",
		"choice4": "164",
		"answer": "c2"
	},
	{
		"question": "6 + 9 ** 0 / 1",
		"choice1": "27",
		"choice2": "15",
		"choice3": "9",
		"choice4": "7",
		"answer": "c4"
	},
	{
		"question": "1 / 1 ** 9 ** 1 / 9 * 9",
		"choice1": "1",
		"choice2": "9",
		"choice3": "27",
		"choice4": "81",
		"answer": "c1"
	},
	{
		"question": "a = 128; a/a+a-a*a/a ",
		"choice1": "0",
		"choice2": "1",
		"choice3": "Infinity",
		"choice4": "-Infinity",
		"answer": "c2"
	},
	{
		"question": "b = 9; b+b**b**b*b",
		"choice1": "81",
		"choice2": "243",
		"choice3": "Infinity",
		"choice4": "-Infinity",
		"answer": "c3"
	},
	{
		"question": "Infinity - 0 - Infinity",
		"choice1": "0",
		"choice2": "Not-A-Number",
		"choice3": "Infinity",
		"choice4": "-Infinity",
		"answer": "c2"
	},
	{
		"question": "a = 1; b = 127; b-a*b/a",
		"choice1": "126",
		"choice2": "127",
		"choice3": "0",
		"choice4": "1",
		"answer": "c3"
	},
	{
		"question": "9 - 8 + 7 - 6 + 5",
		"choice1": "7",
		"choice2": "8",
		"choice3": "9",
		"choice4": "10",
		"answer": "c1"
	},
	{
		"question": "4 * 3 * 2 * 1 ** 0",
		"choice1": "1",
		"choice2": "12",
		"choice3": "24",
		"choice4": "48",
		"answer": "c3"
	},
	{
		"question": "11 / 100 / 11",
		"choice1": "0.9090",
		"choice2": "0.9999",
		"choice3": "0.1010",
		"choice4": "0.0100",
		"answer": "c4"
	}

]
